Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyenhuy-591977212 (LinkedIn) www.behance.net/ nguyenhuyux9392 (Personal)

Top Skills
UI
UX Research
Quality Control

Honors-Awards
DESIGNATHON 2023

Nguyen Huy

UX UI Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I am a UX/UI designer with a passion for creating digital products that are both aesthetically pleasing and user-friendly. I have experience in designing web and mobile applications using design software such as Figma and Adobe Creative Suite. I follow a user-centered design approach, where I conduct research, create prototypes, implement feedback, and collaborate with developers to deliver high-quality design solutions. I also keep myself updated with the latest trends and technologies in UX/UI design

I am a hard-working, creative, and reliable designer who can work well in a team or independently. I have excellent communication and interpersonal skills that make me a good team player and a responsible colleague. I can collaborate with other designers, developers, and stakeholders to deliver high-quality products.

You can see more details about my education, achievements, and experience in my portfolio, which I have attached to this CV along with my contact details. I have also included some examples of my work that demonstrate my UX/UI design skills and abilities. You can reach me at any time via my phone number: 0938 493 010 or email: huyngux9392@gmail.com.

Experience

Green Software Technology Co., Ltd. UX UI Designer
August 2024 - Present (8 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Experienced UX/UI and Graphic Designer at an outsourcing company. I craft intuitive user interfaces and compelling visuals for global clients. Passionate about merging creativity with functionality to deliver impactful designs. Continuously exploring new trends to enhance user experiences and drive engagement.

Fahasa.com UX UI Designer March 2022 - September 2022 (7 months)

Freelance Video Editor July 2019 - 2020 (1 year) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Freelance
Photographer and videographer
July 2013 - 2018 (5 years)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

Keyframe Academy
Certificate, UX UI · (March 2021 - July 2022)

Fpt Arena Multimedia Academy (2011 - 2013)

HCM City University of Foreign languages and Information Technology

· (2010 - 2011)